Preliminary Guide to the Institutional Research Office records, 1971-1990 RG0036
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Institutional Research Office records
1931-1999
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Office of Institutional Research
RG0036
29 Linear Feet
The Office of Institutional Research (OIR) of The George Washington University supports University decision-makers in developing plans to achieve University goals and objectives. Materials in this collection include 1990 report files, PPSBM, Ernst and Whinney, Equal Opportunity Program. The material is dated from 1971-90.
Restrictions on Access
Collection closed for research unless permission granted by originating office.
Acquisition Information
Acqusition data is unknown for this collection.
Historical or Biographical Note
The Office of Institutional Research (OIR) of The George Washington University supports University decision-makers in developing plans to achieve University goals and objectives. OIR works with users to define their information needs and ensures that those needs are met in an accurate and timely manner. OIR serves the internal community of University administrators, faculty, and students and responds to external requirements for data.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include 1990 report files, PPSBM, Ernst and Whinney, Equal Opportunity Program, University Budgets and Teaching Load Reports dating from 1931-1999.
Formerly RG#2.2.2 ACC#75
Collection Organization
Organized into two series: Department Files and Teaching Load Reports.
Washington (D.C.); George Washington University
- Departmental files, 1971-1990; RG0036 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  Materials in this series include 1990 report files, PPSBM, Ernst and Whinney, and Equal Opportunity Program. The material is dated from 1971-90.
  Formerly ACC#75
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.
- University Budgets and Teaching Load Reports, 1931-1999; RG0036 Series 2; 28.5 Linear Feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains University Budgets (1931-32 to 1945-45) and Teaching Load Reports (1963-64 to 1999).
  - University Budgets 1931-32 to 1942-43 (Box 1)
  - University Budgets 1943-44 to 1944-45, Teaching Load Reports 1963-1966, Fall 1979 (Box 2)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1980, Fall 1980, Spring 1981, Fall 1981 (Box 3)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1982,Fall 1982,Spring 1983,Fall 1983 (Box 4)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1984, Fall 1984, Spring 1985,Fall 1985 (Box 5)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1986, Fall 1986, Spring 1987, Fall 1987 (Box 6)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1988, Fall 1988, Spring 1989, Fall 1989 (Box 7)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1990, Fall 1990, Spring 1991, Fall 1991 (Box 8)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1966, Spring 1967, Fall 1967, Spring 1968, Fall 1968, Spring 1969 (Box 9)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1969, Spring 1970, Fall 1970, Spring 1971, Fall 1971, Spring 1972 (Box 10)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1972, Spring 1973, Fall 1973, Spring 1974, Fall 1974, Spring 1975 (Box 11)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1975, Spring 1976, Fall 1976, Spring 1977 (Box 12)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1977, Spring 1978, Fall 1978 (Box 13)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1979, Spring 1992, Fall 1992 (Box 14)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1993, Fall 1993, Spring 1994 (Box 15)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1994, Spring 1995, Fall 1995 (Box 16)
  - Teaching Load Reports Spring 1996,Fall 1996,Spring 1997 (Box 17)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1997, Spring 1998 (Box 18)
  - Teaching Load Reports Fall 1998, Spring 1999, Fall 1999 (Box 19)
- T.A. Coons GWU Institutional research, undated; RG0036 Series 3 (Box 2, Reel 1, Reel 2)
  - Audio tape reel (Box 1)
  - Audio tape reel (Box 2)